sumologic.com 2019-04-10

# Privacy Statement | Sumo Logic

Effective Date: 11/01/2017  
Last Updated: 03/06/2019

This privacy statement applies to [www.sumologic.com](http://www.sumologic.com/) and our service Sumo Logic Service owned and operated by Sumo Logic, Inc. This privacy statement describes how Sumo Logic, Inc. (‘Sumo Logic’, ‘We’, ‘Us’ or ‘Our’) collects and uses the personal information you provide on our Web site [www.sumologic.com](https://www.sumologic.com/) (the “Site”) and our Sumo Logic Services (the “Service”). It also describes the choices available to you regarding our use of your personal information and how you can access and update this information. The use of information collected through our service shall be limited to the purpose of providing the service for which the Client has engaged Sumo Logic.

### EU – U.S. Privacy Shield and Swiss – U.S. Privacy Shield

Sumo Logic participates in and has certified its compliance with the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework and the Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework. Sumo Logic is committed to subjecting all personal data received from European Union (EU) member countries and Switzerland, respectively, in reliance on the Privacy Shield Framework, to the Framework’s applicable Principles. To learn more about the Privacy Shield Frameworks, and to view our certification visit the U.S. Department of Commerce’s Privacy Shield List. [https://www.privacyshield.gov](https://www.privacyshield.gov/list)

Sumo Logic is responsible for the processing of personal data it receives, under each Privacy Shield Framework, and subsequently transfers to a third party acting as an agent on its behalf. Sumo Logic complies with the Privacy Shield Principles for all onward transfers of personal data from the EU and Switzerland, including the onward transfer liability provisions.

With respect to personal data received or transferred pursuant to the Privacy Shield Frameworks, Sumo Logic is subject to the regulatory enforcement powers of the U.S. Federal Trade Commission. In certain situations, Sumo Logic may be required to disclose personal data in response to lawful requests by public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements.

If you have an unresolved privacy or data use concern that we have not addressed satisfactorily, please contact our U.S.-based third party dispute resolution provider (free of charge) at <https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request>.

Under certain conditions, more fully described on the Privacy Shield website <https://www.privacyshield.gov/article?id=How-to-Submit-a-Complaint>, you may be entitled to invoke binding arbitration when other dispute resolution procedures have been exhausted.

### Information Collection and Use

**We collect the following personal information from you**

  * Contact Information such as name, email address, mailing address, phone number
  * Billing Information such as credit card number, and billing address
  * Unique Identifiers such as user name, account number, password
  * Audit logs, on your behalf and in your account only, from one of the following Google apps, depending on source configuration: Admin, Calendar, Drive, Login, Token.

**We also collect the following information from you**

  * Information about your business such as company name, company size, business type
  * Demographic information such as zip code

**We use this information to**

  * Fulfill your order
  * Send you an order confirmation
  * Assess the needs of your business to determine suitable products
  * Send you requested product or service information
  * Send product updates or warranty information
  * Respond to customer service requests
  * Administer your account
  * Send you a newsletter
  * Send you marketing communications
  * Administer contests and sweepstakes you entered, and notify you if you won
  * Respond to your questions and concerns
  * Improve our Web site and marketing efforts
  * Conduct research and analysis

### Third Party Personal Information Collection

**User Data Supplementation**

We obtain information about your company from third party sources, such as the DiscoverOrg and zoominfo, to create more tailored sales experience for the user.

Examples of the types of information that may be obtained from public sources or purchased from third parties and combined with information we already have about your company, may include

Name  
Email address  
Job title and department  
Business phone numbers (general, direct and fax)  
Company name  
Postal address of company  
Business related postal address of person  
Corporate website URLs  
Social Networking URLs  
The date the email message was sent or received  
Email addresses, names and job titles of recipients and senders

### Communications from the Site

**Newsletters**

We will use your name and email address to send our newsletter to you. If you wish to no longer receive these email communications from us you may follow the unsubscribe instructions contained in each email you receive.

**Service-related Announcements**

We will send you strictly service-related announcements on rare occasions when it is necessary to do so. For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance, we might send you an email.

Generally, you may not opt-out of these communications, which are not promotional in nature. If you do not wish to receive them, you have the option to deactivate your account.

**Service providers**

We use other third parties such as an email service provider to send out emails on our behalf, and a web-hosting provider to host our services. When you sign up for our services, we will share your personal information only as necessary for the third party to provide that service. 

**Information Sharing**

We will share your personal information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this privacy statement.

**Legal Disclaimer**

We reserve the right to disclose your personal information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, respond to a government request and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Web site.

If Sumo Logic is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Web site of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information.

**Frames**

Some of our pages utilize framing techniques to serve content to/from our partners while preserving the look and feel of our website. Please be aware that you are providing your personal information to these third parties and not to [www.sumologic.com](https://www.sumologic.com/).

### Access to Personal Information Collected When We Act as a Controller

Upon request Sumo Logic will provide you with information about whether we hold any of your personal information. If your personal information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may correct, update, delete/deactivate it by submitting a form on our Data Subject Access Request Portal at <https://self-service.sumologic.com/dsar>. We will respond to your request to access within 30 days.

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

For audit logs from Google Apps, once ingested into Sumo Logic, you can search for these audit logs within your account.

### Access to Personal Information Collected When We Act as a Processor

**Service Provider Collection/Use**

Sumo Logic collects information under the direction of its Clients, and has no direct relationship with the individuals whose personal data it processes.

**Choice**

We collect information for our clients, if you are a customer of one of our Clients and would no longer like to be contacted by one of our Clients that use our service, please contact the client that you interact with directly.

**Service Provider, Sub Processors/Onward Transfer**

Sumo Logic may transfer personal information to companies that help us provide our service. Transfers to subsequent third parties are covered by the provisions in this Policy regarding notice and choice and the service agreements with our Clients.

**Access to Data Controlled by Our Clients**

Sumo Logic acknowledges that you have the right to access your personal information. Sumo Logic has no direct relationship with the individuals whose personal data it processes. An individual who seeks access, or who seeks to correct, amend, or delete inaccurate data should direct its query to Sumo Logic’s Client (the data controller). If requested to remove data we will respond within 30 days.

**Data Retention**

Sumo Logic will retain personal data we process on behalf of our Clients for as long as needed to provide services to our Client. Sumo Logic will retain this personal information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

### Security

The security of your personal information is important to us. When you log into our service or when you enter sensitive information (such as a credit card number) on our order forms, we encrypt the transmission of information using secure socket layer technology (SSL).

We follow generally accepted standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can contact us at [support@sumologic.com](mailto:support@sumologic.com).

### Cookies and Similar Technologies

Technologies such as: cookies, beacons, tags and scripts are used by Sumo Logic and our partners including marketing automation, heat mapping technology, advertising, demand marketing and web analytics partners. These technologies are used in analyzing trends, administering the site, tracking users’ movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We may receive reports based on the use of these technologies by these companies on an individual as well as aggregated basis.

We use cookies in our order form, to remember users’ settings (e.g. language preference), for authentication. Users can control the use of cookies at the individual browser level. If you reject cookies, you may still use our site, but your ability to use some features or areas of our site may be limited.

**Advertising**

We partner with a third party to either display advertising on our Web site or to manage our advertising on other sites. Our third party partner may use cookies and similar technologies to gather information about your activities on this site and other sites in order to provide you advertising based upon your browsing activities and interests. If you wish to not have this information used for the purpose of serving you interest-based ads, you may opt-out by clicking [here](http://preferences-mgr.truste.com/) (or if located in the European Union click [here](http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/)). Please note this does not opt you out of being served ads. You will continue to receive generic ads.

**Clear Gifs**

Our third party advertising partner employs a software technology called clear gifs (a.k.a. Web Beacons/Web Bugs), that help us better manage content on our site by informing us what content is effective. Clear gifs are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of Web users. In contrast to cookies, which are stored on a user’s computer hard drive, clear gifs are embedded invisibly on Web pages and are about the size of the period at the end of this sentence. We tie the information gathered by clear gifs to our customers’ personal information.

We use clear gifs in our HTML-based emails to let us know which emails have been opened by recipients. This allows us to gauge the effectiveness of certain communications and the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns.

**Log Files**

As is true of most Web sites, we use a third party tracking-utility partner to gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, the files viewed on our site (e.g., HTML pages, graphics, etc.), operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data. We may combine this automatically collected log information with other information we collect about you. We do this to improve services we offer you, to improve marketing, analytics, or site functionality.

We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users’ movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole.

**Local Storage Objects**

We use Local Storage, such as HTML5, to store content information and preferences. Third parties with whom we partner to provide certain features on our website or to display advertising based upon your web browsing activity also use HTML5 to collect and store information. Various browsers may offer their own management tools for removing HTML5. 

### Social Media Features

Our Web site includes Social Media Features, such as the Facebook Like button and Widgets, such as the Share this button or interactive mini-programs that run on our site. These Features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Site. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy statement of the company providing it.

### Links to Other Web Sites

Our Site includes links to other Web sites whose privacy practices may differ from those of Sumo Logic. If you submit personal information to any of those sites, your information is governed by their privacy statements. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy statement of any Web site you visit.

### Public Forums

Our Web site offers publicly accessible blogs or community forums. You should be aware that any information you provide in these areas may be read, collected, and used by others who access them. To request removal of your personal information from our blog or community forum, contact us at [support@sumologic.com](mailto:support@sumologic.com). In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personal information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why. We encourage all users to exercise caution when providing personal information in the blog or community forum.

### Surveys

From time-to-time we may provide you the opportunity to participate in contests or surveys on our site. If you participate, we will request certain personal information from you. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and you therefore have a choice whether or not to disclose this information. The requested information typically includes contact information such as your name, company, and email or telephone number, and demographic information such as your title and the size of company you represent.

We use this information to notify contest winners and award prizes, to monitor site traffic or personalize the site (in the case of anonymous information collected in surveys), to send participants an email newsletter.

We may use a third party service provider to conduct these surveys or contests; that company will be prohibited from using our users’ personal information for any other purpose. We will not share the personal information you provide through a contest or survey with other third parties unless we give you prior notice and choice.

### Referrals

If you choose to use our referral service to tell a friend about our site, we will ask you for your friend’s name and email address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the site. Sumo Logic stores this information for tracking purposes to keep a record of how and when the information was originally obtained.

Your friend may contact us at [support@sumologic.com](mailto:support@sumologic.com) to request that we remove this information from our database.

### Testimonials

We display personal testimonials of satisfied customers on our site in addition to other endorsements. With your consent we may post your testimonial along with your name. If you wish to update or delete your testimonial, you can contact us at [support@sumologic.com](mailto:support@sumologic.com). 

### Notification of Privacy Statement Changes

We may update this privacy statement to reflect changes to our information practices. If we make any material changes we will notify you or our Client by email (sent to the email address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on this Site prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.

### Contact Us

If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy statement, please contact us at [support@sumologic.com](mailto:support@sumologic.com) or via postal mail at

Attn: Compliance Dept  
SUMO LOGIC  
305 Main Street  
Redwood City, CA 94063  
650-810-8700
